var questions = [{
 
                 "question": "what is c language ?",
                 "option1": "programming language",
                 "option2": "OOPS concepts",
                 "option3": "alphabet in english",
                 "option4": "none of this",
                 "answer": "1" 
                },
                {
                     "question": "what is c++ language ?",
                     "option1": "programming language with oops",
                     "option2": "Web application",
                     "option3": "alphabet in english with ++",
                     "option4": "none of this",
                     "answer": "1" 
                },
                {
                     "question": "what is php language ?",
                     "option1": "front end language",
                     "option2": "back end languages ",
                     "option3": "server side languages",
                     "option4": "opt2&3",
                     "answer": "4" 
                },
                {
                     "question": "what is html ?",
                     "option1": "hyper text markup languages",
                     "option2": "hyper talk markup languages",
                     "option3": "hyper text transfer languages",
                     "option4": "none of this",
                     "answer": "1" 
                },
                {
                     "question": "what is css ?",
                     "option1": "casca selector style",
                     "option2": "cat short selector",
                     "option3": "cascading style sheet",
                     "option4": "style on web",
                     "answer": "3" 
                },
                {
                     "question": "what is js ?",
                     "option1": "java languages",
                     "option2": "javascript languages",
                     "option3": "typescript",
                     "option4": "jet script",
                     "answer": "2" 
                },
                {
                     "question": "what is sql ?",
                     "option1": "structual languages",
                     "option2": "query languages",
                     "option3": "command text",
                     "option4": "sequential query languages",
                     "answer": "2" 
                },
                {
                     "question": "what is react ?",
                     "option1": "application programme",
                     "option2": "frameworks",
                     "option3": "javascript frameworks",
                     "option4": "facebook application",
                     "answer": "3" 
                },
                {
                     "question": "Who is ceo of scale ai?",
                     "option1": "mark zuckberg",
                     "option2": "sundari pichai",
                     "option3": "elon musk",
                     "option4": "alexander wang",
                     "answer": "4" 
                },
                {
                     "question": "Who is ceo of pepul social media?",
                     "option1": "george",
                     "option2": "sridhar venbu",
                     "option3": "suresh",
                     "option4": "freshworks",
                     "answer": "3" 
                }
       ]